Infinite Evil
Lurking Fear is a horror, crime film directed by C. Courtney Joyner.
The storm-swept and depopulated town of Leffert’s Corners has been terrorized for decades
by grotesque creatures that breed in the depths beneath the local cemetery.
A group of townspeople have hatched a last-ditch plan to destroy the ghoul-infested graveyard, but their mission is
interrupted by the arrival of a band of violent thieves intent on retrieving money hidden in one of the graves.
Bennett, played by Jon Finch.
John Martense, played by Blake Adams.
Cathryn Farrell, played by Ashley Laurence.
Knaggs, played by Vincent Schiavelli.
Dr. Haggis, played by Jeffrey Combs.
Ms. Marlowe, played by Allison Mackie.
Lurking Fear is a 1994 horror film, loosely based on the H.
Lovecraft short story "The Lurking Fear".
It was produced by Charles Band's Full Moon
Entertainment and written and directed by C.
Courtney Joyner.
It’s an international co-production between the United States and Romania.
The tone is dark.